Preliminary Guide to the Frank Bardacke Papers M2014
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 3: United Farm Workers
  - Subseries 3.3: UFW Tax Documents
    - By Laws of F.I.E.L.D. Farmworkers Institute of Education And Leadership Development, 12 (Box 25, Folder 40)
    - Periodic Report (1 of 3), 12 (Box 25, Folder 41)
    - Periodic Report (2 of 3), 12 (Box 25, Folder 42)
    - Periodic Report (3 of 3), 12 (Box 25, Folder 43)
    - Periodic Report (1 of 3), 12 (Box 25, Folder 44)
    - Periodic Report (2 of 3), 12 (Box 25, Folder 45)
    - Periodic Report (3 of 3), 12 (Box 25, Folder 46)
    - Registration Form (1 of 3), 12 (Box 25, Folder 47)
    - Registration Form (2 of 3), 12 (Box 25, Folder 48)
    - Registration Form (3 of 3), 12 (Box 25, Folder 49)
    - Periodic Report, 12 (Box 25, Folder 50)
    - Miscellaneous Material, 12 (Box 25, Folder 51)
  - Subseries 3.4: UFW and Farmworker Publications; Bardecke Notes
    - Malcriado, 16 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Jodi K. Draper, 16 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - El Obrero Newspaper, 16 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - El Obrero Newspaper, 16 (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - El Obrero Newspaper, 16 (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - Teamsters (Packer), 16 (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - Adair, 16 (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - Adair, 16 (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - Stacey Staaden Tafoya, 16 (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - Adair, 16 (Box 26, Folder 31)
    - Adair on the President, NL 5/1/77, 16 (Box 26, Folder 32)
    - Adair, Cal Poly, Archive, 16 (Box 26, Folder 33)
    - Doug Adair, 16 (Box 26, Folder 34)
    - Miscellaneous Material, 16 (Box 26, Folder 35)
    - Newspaper: El Malcriado [photocopies], 16 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Newspaper: El Malcriado [photocopies], 16 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Newspaper: El Malcriado [photocopies], 16 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Newspaper: El Malcriado [photocopies], 16 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Newspaper: El Malcriado [photocopies], 16 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Newspaper: El Malcriado [photocopies], 16 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Newspaper: El Malcriado [photocopies], 16 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Newspaper: El Malcriado [photocopies], 16 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Newspaper: El Malcriado [photocopies], 16 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Newspaper: El Malcriado [photocopies], 16 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Newspaper: El Malcriado [photocopies], 16 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Newspaper: El Malcriado [photocopies], 16 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Newspaper: El Malcriado [photocopies], 16 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Newspaper: El Malcriado [photocopies], 16 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Newspaper: El Malcriado [photocopies], 16 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Newspaper: El Malcriado [photocopies], 16 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Newspaper: El Malcriado [photocopies], 16 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Newspaper: El Malcriado [photocopies], 16 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Newspaper: El Malcriado [photocopies], 16 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Newspaper: El Malcriado [photocopies], 16 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Subseries 3.5: Agricultural Labor Relations Board
    - Agricultural Labor Relations Board Nov. 24, 2004, 23 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - First Annual Report of the Agricultural Labor Relations Board 1976-77, 23 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Second Annual Report of the Agricultural Labor Relations Board 1978, 23 (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Third Annual Report of the Agricultural Labor Relations Board 1979, 23 (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - First Annual Report of the Agricultural Labor Relations Board 1980, 23 (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Agricultural Labor Relations Boards Annual Report to the Legislature 1981-82, 23 (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - Agricultural Labor Relations Boards Annual Report to the Legislature 1982-83, 23 (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - Agricultural Labor Relations Boards Annual Report to the Legislature 1983-84, 23 (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - Agricultural Labor Relations Boards Annual Report to the Legislature 1984-85, 23 (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - Agricultural Labor Relations Boards Annual Report to the Legislature 1985-86, 23 (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - Agricultural Labor Relations Boards Annual Report to the Legislature 1986-87, 23 (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - Agricultural Labor Relations Boards Annual Report to the Legislature 1987-88, 23 (Box 35, Folder 26)
    - Agricultural Labor Relations Boards Annual Report to the Legislature 1988-90, 23 (Box 35, Folder 27)
    - Agricultural Labor Relations Boards Annual Report to the Legislature 1989-90, 23 (Box 35, Folder 28)
    - Agricultural Labor Relations Boards Annual Report to the Legislature 1990-91, 23 (Box 35, Folder 29)
    - Agricultural Labor Relations Boards Annual Report to the Legislature 1991-92, 23 (Box 35, Folder 30)
    - Agricultural Labor Relations Boards Annual Report to the Legislature 2000-2002, 23 (Box 35, Folder 31)
    - Agricultural Labor Relations Boards Annual Report to the Legislature 1999 - 2000, 23 (Box 35, Folder 32)
    - Agricultural Labor Relations Boards Annual Report to the Legislature 1989-99, 23 (Box 35, Folder 33)
    - Agricultural Labor Relations Boards Annual Report to the Legislature 1996-1998, 23 (Box 35, Folder 34)
    - Agricultural Labor Relations Boards Annual Report to the Legislature 1994-1996, 23 (Box 35, Folder 35)
  - Subseries 3.6: Alinsky Materials
    - Agricultural Labor Relations Boards Annual Report to the Legislature 1992-94, 23 (Box 35, Folder 36)
    - David Martinez Contract and Others To Do, 20 (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Oxnard Press, 20 (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - Oxnard, 20 (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - Mex/Am E Mex AG Labor, 20 (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - Get out if You Can, 20 (Box 33, Folder 25)
    - Democracy Notes, 20 (Box 33, Folder 26)
    - "Beyond the Politics of Place" by Mike Miller, 20 (Box 33, Folder 27)
    - And Classroom, 20 (Box 33, Folder 28)
    - Cesar Chavez talks about Organizing and the History of the NFWA, 20 (Box 33, Folder 29)
    - Bill Leverrer Manuscript (1 of 3), 20 (Box 33, Folder 30)
    - Bill Leverrer Manuscript (2 of 3), 20 (Box 33, Folder 31)
    - Bill Leverrer Manuscript (3 of 3), 20 (Box 33, Folder 32)
    - What is this? Manuscript, 20 (Box 33, Folder 33)
    - Miscellaneous Material, 20 (Box 33, Folder 34)
    - Finding and Making Leaders, 20 (Box 33, Folder 35)
    - Various Notes, 20 (Box 33, Folder 36)
    - Miscellaneous Material, 20 (Box 33, Folder 37)
    - Various Notes, 20 (Box 33, Folder 38)
    - Miscellaneous Material, 20 (Box 33, Folder 39)
    - Various Manuscripts, 20 (Box 33, Folder 40)
    - Various Notes, 20 (Box 33, Folder 41)
  - Series 3.7: Marshall Ganz Material
    - 1979 Marshall Report, IIIA (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Granz M. Report, IIIA (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Granz Boineke, IIIA (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Marshall/Levy, IIIA (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Granz C.W. Interview 1986, IIIA (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Marshall on 78-81, IIIA (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Marshall Questions 06, IIIA (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Marshall, IIIA (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Marshall 's [last], IIIA (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Granz Tables, IIIA (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Marshall Veg Industry Plan, IIIA (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Ganz Emails, IIIA (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Model 77 Agreement 1979 Contract Proposal, IIIA (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Questions for Marshall, IIIA (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Granz 1969 Memo on locals and Memo on Italy Boycott, IIIA (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Marshall to Lenon 9/26/79, IIIA (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Granz/Chewey Letters, IIIA (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Five Smooth Stones, IIIA (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Calender 1957-1967, IIIA (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - To Pony Express (1 of 2), IIIA (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - To Pony Express (2 of 2), IIIA (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Miscellaneous Material, IIIA (Box 20, Folder 22)
- Series 4: Research Files
  - Subseries 4.1: Research Files
    - "La Causa" El Movimiento de Los Trabajadores Agricolas en California (1 of 2), 10 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - "La Causa" El Movimiento de Los Trabajadores Agricolas en California (2 of 2), 10 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Comparacion de Condiciones y Contratos en el Valle de Salinas (1 of 2), 10 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Comparacion de Condiciones y Contratos en el Valle de Salinas (2 of 2), 10 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Thesis by James Fraysier, 10 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Margo Oral History, 10 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Border Patrol, 10 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Mex American Death Rate in Vietnam, 10 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous Material, 10 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - A Historical Economic Analysis of the Wage Structure of the California Fruit... By Martin Louis Brown (1 of 5), 10 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - A Historical Economic Analysis of the Wage Structure of the California Fruit... By Martin Louis Brown (2 of 5), 10 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - A Historical Economic Analysis of the Wage Structure of the California Fruit... By Martin Louis Brown (3 of 5), 10 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - A Historical Economic Analysis of the Wage Structure of the California Fruit... By Martin Louis Brown (4 of 5), 10 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - A Historical Economic Analysis of the Wage Structure of the California Fruit... By Martin Louis Brown (5 of 5), 10 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Jim UC On Unions, 10 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Joe Nevins, 10 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Inventing Jews, 10 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - IS Conference, 10 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Semilla Newspaper, 10 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Rural California Report, 10 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Immigration, 10 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Farm Workers, 10 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Research, 10 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - A Summary of Hard Tomatoes, Hard Times by Jim Hightower, 10 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Labor: Farmworkers Pesticides, 10 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Mexican Labor, 10 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Bibliography, 10 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Mexican Immigration, 11 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Bud Article, 11 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Gender: Women Ag Workers/Ventura CA, 11 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - poster, water damage: requires conservation (Othertype 55)
  - Subseries 4.2: Oral Interviews
    - Chaffee, 9 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - UC Berkeley B Neg 1051 (1 of 3), 9 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - UC Berkeley B Neg 1051 (2 of 3), 9 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - UC Berkeley B Neg 1051 (3 of 3), 9 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Corridos Sin Rostro, 9 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - United Farm Workers of America "Fighting for Our Lives", 9 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Cesar E. Chavez Celebration of Life 1927-1993, 9 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - "No Grapes", 9 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - UC Berkeley 618:11 (1 of 3), 9 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - UC Berkeley 618:11 (2 of 3), 9 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - UC Berkeley 618:11 (2 of 3), 9 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Subseries 4.3: Published Materials
    - Farm Labor 1963, 8 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Farm Labor 1964 (1 of 2), 8 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Farm Labor 1964 (2 of 2), 8 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Farm Labor 1965 (1 of 2), 8 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Farm Labor 1965 (2 of 2), 8 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Farm Labor 1966, 8 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Farm Labor 1967, 8 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Violations of Free Speech and Rights of Labor Feb. - June 1942, 8 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Violations of Free Speech and Rights of Labor Oct. 1942, 8 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Violations of Free Speech and Rights of Labor May 1943 - April 1944, 8 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Violations of Free Speech and Rights of Labor April - May 1944, 8 (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Violations of Free Speech and Rights of Labor January 1940, 8 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Violations of Free Speech and Rights of Labor July 1940 (1 of 3), 8 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Violations of Free Speech and Rights of Labor July 1940 (2 of 3), 8 (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - Violations of Free Speech and Rights of Labor July 1940 (3 of 3), 8 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Texas FW, 8 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Peregrinacion, 8 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Voces del Campo Voices from the the Fields, 8 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Little Notebooks, 13 (Box 25, Folder 52)
  - Subseries 4.4: Correspondence; Notebooks; Graduate Student Papers
    - Notebook, 13 (Box 25, Folder 53)
    - Notebook, 13 (Box 25, Folder 54)
    - Notebook, 13 (Box 25, Folder 55)
    - Miscellaneous Notebook, 13 (Box 25, Folder 56)
    - Miscellaneous Picture, 13 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Hammerback and Jensen, 13 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Chavez Quotes, 13 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Various Notes, 13 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Various Notes, 13 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Farmworker Movement Documentation Project, 13 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Various Newspapers, 13 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Various Newspapers, 13 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - The Farmworker Living on the Margin, 13 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Mike Miller, 13 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Mike Miller, 13 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Alinsky, 13 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - The People Fight Back, 13 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - A Community Organizer's Tale, 13 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Mike Miller, 13 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Letters 1968 Mike Miller, 13 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Miller, Mike, 13 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous Material, 13 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Organizing for Family and Congregation, 13 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Various Articles, 13 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Various Articles, 13 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Subseries 4.5: Published and Unpublished Articles re: Calfornia Agriculture
    - New Migrants vs. Old Migrants: Alternative Market Structures... By Richard Mines and Ricardo Anzaldua, 17A (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Mechanization and Mexican Labor in California Agriculture by David Runsten and Phillip LeVeen, 17A (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - The Bracero in Orange County, California: A work Force for Economic Transition, 17A (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - California Farmworker Housing, 17A (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Regulation of the Farm Labor Market, 17A (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Survey of Research on the Impacts of Pesticides on Agricultural Wokers and the Rural Environment, 17A (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Anthropological Perspectives on Transnational Communities in Rural California, 17A (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Latino Political Participation in Rural California, 17A (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - California's Rural Poor: Trends, Correlates, and Policies, 17A (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - The California Farm Labor Market, 17A (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Farm Restructuring and Employment in California Agriculture, 17A (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - California's Agriculture Dilemma: Higher Production and Lower Wages, 17A (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Annual Farm Labor Report 1965, 17A (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Various Articles, 17A (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - California's Number One Industry Under Attack, 17A (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Destalking the Wily Tomato, 17A (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Giannini Foundation, 17A (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Divide and Conquer: The Legal Foundations of Postwar U.S. Labor Policy, 17A (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Solidarity with the United Farm Workers of America, 17A (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Influence of Faith: Cesar Chavez and the Delano Movement, 17A (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - California Crop Trends: Yields, Acreages, and Production Areas, 17A (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - Agricultural Research, 17A (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - California History Spring 1995, 17A (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - The Californians, 17A (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - Farm Labor Needs and Farm Workers in California 1970 and 1989, 17A (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - University of Pennsylvania Journal of Labor and Employment Law, 17A (Box 31, Folder 26)
    - Southwest Economy Society, 17A (Box 31, Folder 27)
    - Various Articles, 17A (Box 31, Folder 28)
    - Various Notes, 17A (Box 31, Folder 29)
    - Farm Employment and Wage Rates 1910 - 1990, 17A (Box 31, Folder 30)
    - "A Social History of Farm Labor in California... Emphasis on UFW and CRLA" Casper 1984, 17A (Box 31, Folder 31)
    - Green Card Labor... by Richard A. Fineberg, 17A (Box 31, Folder 32)
    - California Agriculture Studies 91-4, 17A (Box 31, Folder 33)
    - California Agricultural Studies, 17A (Box 31, Folder 34)
    - Miscellaneous Material, 17A (Box 31, Folder 35)
    - Impact of Reduced Water Supplies on Central Valley, 17 (Box 31, Folder 36)
    - Apple Costs, 17 (Box 31, Folder 37)
    - Rural California Report, 17 (Box 31, Folder 38)
    - Rural California Report, 17 (Box 31, Folder 39)
    - Agricultural Workers in Central California, Phase II, 1990-91, 17 (Box 31, Folder 40)
    - Migrant Farmworkers: Pursuing Security in an Unstable Labor Market, 17 (Box 31, Folder 41)
    - U.S. Farmworkers in the Post - IRCA Period, 17 (Box 31, Folder 42)
    - California Agriculture Volume 44, 17 (Box 31, Folder 43)
    - DRSC Focus, 17 (Box 31, Folder 44)
    - California Vegetable Crops, 17 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - California Farmer October 1995, 17 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - A Survey of Oaxacan Village Networks in California Agriculture, 17 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - California Agricultural Employment And Earnings Bulletin, 17 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - California Findings from the National Agricultural Workers Survey, 17 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - California Agricultural Studies, 17 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Semilla, 17 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Annual Averages 1992, 17 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Frank Bartekey, 17 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - California Agricultural Studies, 17 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - California Agricultural Studies 90-6, 17 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Agricultural Employment Calendar Year 1991, 17 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - California Findings from the National Agricultural Workers Survey, 17 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Farmworkers in California July 1998, 17 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Report of the Commission on Agricultural Workers, 17 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - SAWs, Raws, and Farmworkers, 17 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - California Agricultural Studies, 17 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - California Agricultural Studies, 17 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - California Agricultural Studies, 17 (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - California Agricultural Studies, 17 (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - California Agricultural Studies, 17 (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - A Demographic and Employment Profile of Persistable Crop Farm Workers, 17 (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - Aug. - Sept. 75, I (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Subseries 4.6: Clippings; Miscellaneous Publications; Print Materials; etc.
    - 10/1/1975, I (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Nov.-Dec. 75, I (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - 76, I (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - 77, I (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Notes on Clips, I (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Clips, I (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - 78, I (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Jan., I (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Feb, I (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - March, I (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - April, I (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - May, I (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - June, I (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - July, I (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - August, I (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Sept, I (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - October, I (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - 11/1/1979, I (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - 12/1/1979, I (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - 8/1/1980, I (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - 1985, IA (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - 1986, IA (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - 1983, IA (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - 1984, IA (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - 1987, IA (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - 1988, IA (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - LA Times - July, IA (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - No Date, IA (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - 81 ND and Guide, IB (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - 1/1/1980, IB (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - 2/1/1980, IB (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - ND 80, IB (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - 3/1/1980, IB (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - 4/1/1980, IB (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - 5/1/1980, IB (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - 6/1/1980, IB (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - 7/1/1980, IB (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - 9/1/1980, IB (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - 10/1/1980, IB (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - 11/1/1980, IB (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - 12/1/1980, IB (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - 1/1/1981, IB (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - 2/1/1981, IB (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - 3/1/1981, IB (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - 4/1/1981, IB (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - 5/1/1981, IB (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - 6/1/1981, IB (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - 7/1/1981, IB (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - 8/1/1981, IB (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - 9/1/1981, IB (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - 10/1/1981, IB (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - 11/1/1981, IB (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - 12/1/1981, IB (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - 1/1/1982, IB (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - 2/1/1982, IB (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - 3/1/1982, IB (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - 4/1/1982, IB (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - 5/1/1982, IB (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - 6/1/1982, IB (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - 7/1/1982, IB (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - 8/1/1982, IB (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - 9/1/1982, IB (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - 10/1/1982, IB (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - 11/1/1982, IB (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - 12/1/1982, IB (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - RPE 1974, II (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - 7/11/1973, II (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Fresno 1971-72, II (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - Fresno B 1966-68, II (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - Delano Record, II (Box 16, Folder 42)
    - Fresno Bee 1973, II (Box 16, Folder 43)
    - Malcriado 1974, II (Box 16, Folder 44)
    - California Farmer 73-74, II (Box 16, Folder 45)
    - [Bark Culiy], II (Box 16, Folder 46)
    - Tracker 1973, II (Box 16, Folder 47)
    - Pajaroni 1970-74, II (Box 16, Folder 48)
    - LA Times 73 Strike, II (Box 16, Folder 49)
    - Precher 75-76-77, II (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Malcriado 1973, II (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - 1961 Imperial Valley Sliche, II (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - LA Times 68, II (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Tulare Advance Register, II (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Lily Espinoza, II (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Pacher 74-75, II (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Texas Interlude, II (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - FMNS 1973, II (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous Material, II (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - RPE 1973, II (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - NYT 1973, II (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Bacon Lies on View, IIA (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - LA Times '76 Selections, IIA (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - LA Time 74-75, IIA (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Newspaper Print-Outs, IIA (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Random Articles, IIA (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Misc. Articles, IIA (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - IV Press Nov 79 - Feb 80, IIA (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Riverside Enterprise, IIA (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Bakersfield Calif, IIA (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - [Minimal... 1973], IIA (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - LA Times 1971-72, IIA (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Landa Rosebraugh, IIA (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Salinas California 1970, IIA (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - SF Chronicle 1950s, IIA (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - SF Chronicle, IIA (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - NYT 1972, IIA (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Summary LA Times 11/17/68, IIA (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Culture Farm Labor Repeat (1962), III (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Culture Farm Labor Repeat (1964), III (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Edelman/Schrade Mails, III (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - AWOC Paper, III (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Bibliographies/Sources, III (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Monthly Labor Review, III (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - BIDS, III (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - March to Sacramento, III (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - NFWA Constitutions, III (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - NFWA/NFWC Constitutions, III (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - Pirelli - Munetti Boycott (66/67), III (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - SWCC 1965/6, III (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - Miscellaneous Material, III (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Farm Labor, III (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Daniel Thesis, III (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Agricultural, III (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Wyeter Thesis, III (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Grape Statistics (Janiesu), III (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - California Fresh Fruit (1964), III (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - The Growers, III (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Grapes (1962), III (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Metzler Studies (1964), III (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Metzler #2, III (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Thompson Thesis (AWOC), III (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Migratory Labor Committee, III (Box 18, Folder 13)